herbergers.com 2016-04-21

# Privacy Policy & Security Procedures - Herberger's

This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 16, 2015.

This website is owned and operated by The Bon-Ton Department Stores, Inc., and this Privacy Policy applies to the website only.

We have posted this Privacy Policy here to inform you of the information we may collect, how it is handled and your rights to opt out of information disclosure. We value our customers and understand your concerns about privacy. Therefore, we have instituted policies intended to ensure your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner.

This Privacy Policy includes examples of the types of personal information we collect. We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us. We do, however, share your information with third parties under certain circumstances. We use this information for marketing and promotional purposes and to service your account. The examples provided below are illustrative and should not be considered a complete inventory of our information collection, use and sharing practices.

### Information We May Collect

The Bon-Ton may collect personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information that we receive from you when using our website. This personal information is gathered when you use our website to register, make a purchase, write a product review and create a registry. Similar personal information is gathered when you register with one of our other services such as mobile or social media applications, such as Facebook.  In order to bill you for your purchase we may collect credit card information including your card type, credit card number, and expiration date. We also collect shipping address information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address and phone number of the intended recipient;
  * Information we receive from you (or that is provided to us on your behalf) on applications, contest entry forms, survey responses and other forms you submit to us, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, Social Security number and income;
  * Information about your transactions with The Bon-Ton or others, such as your purchasing preferences;
  * And information from consumer reporting agencies, providers of marketing and demographic information and data collection agencies, such as customer names and mailing addresses, and information about your credit worthiness.

### Information We May Disclose And To Whom We May Disclose Information

#### Disclosures Permitted By Law

The Bon-Ton may disclose your personal information without your consent as permitted by law. For example, we may use non-affiliated parties to perform services for us, such as providing customer assistance and customer billing, shipping merchandise that you purchased online, and billing your credit card for purchases.  We may disclose your personal information to consumer reporting agencies. We also may disclose information in response to requests from law enforcement agencies or in response to a subpoena or court order.

#### Other Disclosures

We may disclose the personal information we collect to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to companies that offer products or services you may find of value or to other financial institutions, such as insurers, with whom we have marketing agreements.

We may share your personally-identifiable information, including your name, address, email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our advertising partner will make the data we provide it anonymous. To learn more about the use of this information or choose not to have this information used by our third-part advertising partner by option out, please visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Identification may be required for returns. Customer information taken during a return is shared with a 3rd party for the sole purpose of authorizing returns. Customer information captured for authorizations will not be used for marketing purposes.

### Information Regarding Former Customers

The Bon-Ton does not disclose personal information about former customers or customers with inactive accounts, except in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Information Regarding Children

We recognize the importance of protecting the safety and privacy of children. We comply fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age except as permitted by law.

### Our Security Procedures

The security of your personal information is important to us. To prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures. We restrict access to personal information about you to those employees whom we determine have a legitimate business purpose to access such information in connection with the provision of products or services to you. We provide training and communications programs designed to educate employees about the meaning and requirements of our strict standards for data security and confidentiality. We employ industry standard security techniques designed to protect our customer data, including encryption technology, such as “Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to protect your personal information during data transfer.

### Definition Of And How We Use "Cookies"

A "cookie" is a small file stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser that allows our website to recognize you every time you visit our site. No personal identifiable information about you is stored in the cookies. On our site, cookies are used to keep a list of: pages that you clicked on during your visit; items you have selected for printing; and items you have put on your shopping list or placed in the Shopping Bag. We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, click here.

It is your choice to not accept cookies. The "Help" menu of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. However, because cookies allow you to take full advantage of all features on our website, for the best experience we recommend you leave cookies enabled.

### Email Marketing

Use the unsubscribe link on any of our promotional or marketing emails to opt-out of receiving email from us.  Please allow up to 10 business days for your request to be processed.

### Mobile Text Alerts

By opting in to mobile text alerts, the Bon-Ton customer agrees to receive a maximum of 3 marketing text messages per week. The text messages are generated by an automated dialer from Bon-Ton to the provided mobile number. The Bon-Ton customer understands that consent is not required as a condition to make a purchase. Message and data rates may apply. Text HELP for more information or STOP to 266866 to opt-out of receiving text messages.

Bon-Ton collects certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use, device identifier, your mobile operating system, pages you visit on our mobile site, search terms, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use and information about the way you use our mobile website and applications.

Read the Mobile Terms & Conditions

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

By interacting with us, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify or supplement this Privacy Policy at any time, and we encourage you to review it periodically. If we make material changes, we will provide current customers with a revised notice that describes our new practices.

### **California Privacy Rights**

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To request a copy of this information or to opt out of these disclosures, please contact us as indicated below.

### Your Preference

If you prefer that we do not disclose your personal information to non-affiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures; that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law). If you wish to opt out of disclosures to non-affiliated third parties, you may mail a written request, along with your name, address and account number, to the following address:

**The Bon-Ton Department Stores, Inc.**  
_Corporate Office_  
2801 East Market Street  
York, PA 17405

Or call the following toll-free number:   
1-800-945-4438, 6am-12am (CST) Monday -Sunday

If you have a joint account, a request by one party will apply to the entire account. Please allow approximately 10 weeks for your request to take effect.
